So you're still hungry, baby sweeties?
你还很饿吗   宝贝 甜心
Yeah, can I have that?
是的   我能吃那个吗
What do you want?
你想要吃什么
That.
那个
What, the bread?
要什么  面包吗
Yeah.
嗯
Or do you want...
还是来一点
some of the yummy lemon loaf?
还是来一点好吃的柠檬面包呢
What loaf? Give me loaf.
什么面包   给面包
Lemon loaf.
柠檬面包
Where the heck did you get the lemon loaf? From mommy?
柠檬面包哪里来的   妈妈做的吗
I baked it special for Tweedy.
我特意为特维迪做的
No, you didn't. No, you didn't bake it.
不  不是你做的  不 不是你烤的面包
No, you know me too well.
是的   你真了解我
No, no, you didn't bake it.
不   不   不是你烤的面包
No, you didn't... No, you didn't bake it.
不  不是你烤的   你没有烤这个面包
Grandma Marlene baked it.
是奶奶马琳烤的面包
Hmm, yeah.
嗯   是的
You know that mummy can't cook.
你知道妈妈不会烧饭
Hum-em, huh.
嗯咯
Ha ha ha...
哈哈哈